

JAKE RICHARDSON

DETAILS

EMAIL: jakerichardson13@googlemail.com

PHONE: 07894042760

WEBSITE: jakerichardson.co

ADDRESS:

12 Nangreaves Street, Leigh, WN7 4TN

SKILLS

HTML	
CSS / SASS	
JS / JQUERY	
AJAX	
LARAVEL	
CODEIGNITOR	

REFERENCES

ROB HALLIWELL: Technology Director, 120 Bolton Road, Atherton, M46 9JZ

TOM PUDDIFOOT: Technology Leader,
Dovecote House,
Old Hall Road,
M33 2GS

ABOUT

An enthusistic and motivated PHP software developer seeking further career progression. Two years commercial development at LGH and General Electric. Currently re-developing two CMS systems which will be transitioned from raw PHP to Laravel. Previous vast experience with BigCommerce and Shopify custom theme development as well as ample knowledge of Wordpress. Strong passion and understanding of front end design with a embedded knowledge of user interaction. Successfully developed and managed a male online clothing company, JMR Clothing, from 2015 to 2018. Avid rugby league enthusiast and Wigan Warriors supporter.

EXPERIENCE

LGH: Junior Software Developer (2019-Present)

Tasks: Laravel development, Codelgniter development, PHP, jQuery, JavaScript, Sass, Git versioning (using BitBucket), MySQL, Ajax, DeployHQ and weekly sales reporting development.

GENERAL ELECTRIC: Intern Web Developer (2017 - 2018) Tasks: BigCommerce theme development, HTML, CSS, jQuery, JavaScript, 3D modelling, Git

JMR CLOTHING: Owner (2016 - 2018)

Tasks: Shopify theme development, product design, product manufacturing, sales reporting and customer support.

EDUCATION

versioning.

LEEDS BECKETT UNIVERSITY: BSc Computing (2015 - 2019) 2:2 Classification

WIGAN & LEIGH COLLEGE: Level 3 Computing Diploma Distinction*